Rescue crews pulled a man to safety after a collapse at a construction site in
Brooklyn on Tuesday.
The incident happened on the 400 block of Rutland Road just after 1230 pm.
Rescue crews pulled a man to safety after a at a construction site in Brooklyn on
Tuesday. The incident happened on the 400 block of Rutland Road just after 1230 pm.
Rescue crews pulled a man to safety after a collapse at a construction site in
Brooklyn on Tuesday.
The incident happened on the 400 block of Rutland Road just after 1230 pm.
The Fire Department of New York says the vacant 100 -year -old building being pulled
down partially collapsed.
A man described as a non -worker civilian was buried up to his waist in the
basement. The man was collecting building materials when the first floor collapsed
underneath him. A man described as a non -worker civilian was buried up to his waist
in the basement.
The man was collecting building materials when the first floor collapsed underneath
him. A man described as a non -worker civilian was buried up to his waist in the
basement. The man was collecting building materials when the first floor collapsed
underneath him. He was trapped under a beam about 10 feet below the surface for
nearly an hour and a The man was then taken to hospital.
He was trapped under a about 10 feet below the surface for nearly an hour and a
half. The man was then taken to hospital.
was trapped under a beam about 10 feet below the surface for nearly an hour and a
half. The man was then taken to
Officials said he is in stable condition with non -life -threatening injuries.
The building was reportedly purchased by a neighboring church in 2011.
The building was reportedly purchased